# CURRICULUM VITAE ANDREW QUINN

2260 Hayward Street Ann Arbor, MI 48105 Phone: 1.630.453.1899
Email: arquinn@umich.edu
Web: web.eecs.umich.edu/~arquinn

## INTRODUCTION

I am a Microsoft Research Fellow and a National Science Foundation Graduate Research Fellow.

My dissertation applies techniques from data-intensive computing, such as cluster-scale parallelization and declarative languages, to software reliability tasks like debugging, security forensics, and data provenance. I have mentored and advised students who work on projects to improve the reliability of applications that use emerging hardware, including persistent memory and edge computing.

# **EDUCATION**

University of Michigan

Ph.D., Computer Science and Engineering

University of Michigan

M.S., Computer Science and Engineering

M.S., Computer Science and Engineering

Computer Science and Engineering

Computer Science and B.A., Mathematics

Honors: summa cum laude, Phi Beta Kappa, Deans List

Ann Arbor, MI

(Sep 2015–May 2015)

Computer Science and B.A., Mathematics

(Aug 2010–May 2014)

#### FELLOWSHIPS AND AWARDS

1. Microsoft Research Fellowship.	Two year fellowship awarded to nine	(2017)
early-career Ph.D. students		

- 2. National Science Foundation Graduate Student Research Fellowship. (2017)
  Three year fellowship awarded to early-career Ph.D. students
- 3. John L. Gilpatrick Mathematics Award, Denison University. Awarded to the most outstanding senior major in the Math and CS department (2014)
- 4. Ted Barclay Top Five Student Athlete, Denison University. Awarded to the top five student athletes at Denison University based on GPA.

### PEER-REVIEWED PUBLICATIONS

- 1. Ian Neal, Ben Reeves, Ben Stoler, **Andrew Quinn**, Youngjin Kwon, Simon Peter and Baris Kasikci. *Agamotto: How Persistent is your Persistent Memory Application?*. In Proceedings of the 2020 USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). November 2020. Acceptance Rate: 70/398 = 17.6%
- Matt Furlong, Andrew Quinn, and Jason Flinn.
   The case for Determinism on the Edge. In 2nd USENIX Workshop on Hot Topics in Edge Computing (HotEdge). July 2019 Acceptance Rate: 22/39 = 56%
- 3. Andrew Quinn, Michael Cafarella, and Jason Flinn.

  You can't debug what you can't see: Expanding observability with the OmniTable. In Proceedings of the Workshop on Hot Topics in Operating Systems (HotOS). May 2019 Acceptance Rate: 30/125 = 24%
- 4. Andrew Quinn, Jason Flinn, and Michael Cafarella.

  Sledgehammer: Cluster-fueled Debugging. In Proceedings of the 2018 USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). October 2018. Acceptance Rate: 47/264 = 17.8%
- 5. **Andrew Quinn**, David Devecsery, Peter M. Chen and Jason Flinn.

  JetStream: Cluster-scale Parallelization of Information Flow Queries. In Proceedings of the 2016 USENIX

Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI). November 2016. Acceptance Rate: 47/267=17.6%

# PRESENTATIONS

1. You can't debug what you can't see: Expanding Observability with the OmniTable. Workshop on Hot Topics in Operating Systems (HotOS)	(May 2019)
2. <b>Sledgehammer: Cluster-fueled Debugging</b> . USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI)	(Oct 2018)
3. <b>JetStream: Cluster-Scale Parallelization of Information Flow Queries</b> . USENIX Symposium on Operating Systems Design and Implementation (OSDI)	(Nov 2016)
4. Power Management for Malleable Job Scheduling. Denison University department of Math and Computer Science FaST talk	(Apr 2014)
TEACHING EXPERIENCE	
1. <b>Graduate Student Instructor</b> . Data Structures and Algorithms, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI	(May 2019–Jun 2019)
2. Computer Science Drop-in Tutor. Introduction to Computer Science, Denison University, Granville, OH	(Jan 2012–May 2014)
PROFESSIONAL SERVICE	
1. External Review Committee Member. Architectural Support for Programming Languages and Operating Systems (ASPLOS)	(2021)
2. Shadow Program Committee Member. European Conference on Computer Systems (EuroSys)	(2021)
3. <b>Ph.D. Admissions Committee Member</b> . University of Michigan Department of Computer Science and Engineering	(2018)
PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE	
1. <b>Graduate Student</b> . Advisor: Dr. Jason Flinn and Dr. Peter Chen, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI	(Sep 2015–Present)
2. Research Intern in the Systems Group. Mentor: Dr. Suman Nath, Microsoft Corp., Redmond, WA	(May 2017–Aug 2017)
3. <b>Software Development Engineer</b> . International Business Machines (IBM), Dublin, OH	(Jun 2014–Aug 2015)
4. Research Assistant in Online Algorithms. Mentor: Dr. Jessen Havill, Denison University, Granville, OH	(Aug 2013–May 2014 (May 2012–Aug 2012
5. <b>Software Development Engineering Intern</b> . International Business Machines (IBM), Dublin, OH	(May 2013–Aug 2013
OUTREACH ACTIVITIES	
1. Discover Engineering. University of Michigan, Ann Arbor, MI	(Aug 2019)
2. <b>Techie Club</b> . Georgian Heights Elementary, Columbus, OH	(Aug 2014–Aug 2015
3. A Call to College. Newark Elementary Schools, Newark, OH	(Sep 2012–Dec 2013)